Praise and thanks to Allah SWT, who has bestowed abundant grace and blessings upon us all
so that we may always do good and be of benefit to others
Anindosta, or Animasi Indonesia Semesta, is an organization that manages an animation studio
working in futuristic 3D animated film and digital comics in Bogor
Anindosta itself was founded in 2014 on the principle of building up animated filmmaking in Indonesia
especially in the action and sci-fi genres
Our project is titled Volter Stein - The Ultimate Law Enforcement, the story of a teenager named Arlo
who must go through a long journey at his very young age to restore peace to his planet
which has been taken over by an evil force called "Black Bug"
this project is planned to premiere in 2025, since we have not yet secured the production cost
needed to carry out this project
which will eventually be produced as 27 episodes
with each episode running around 20-25 minutes
over a production period of about 1-2 years
the first year for research, and the second year for production
we are currently producing a serialized digital comic that has already been published on the Webtoon platform
to introduce each character's traits through spin-off stories of their daily lives
one thing we firmly believe is that there is great future potential few people are aware of
this great potential in animated film can be used to grow young people's creativity and, of course, reduce unemployment in Indonesia
so that young people can be creative and pour their imaginative ideas out here at home
That's all I can share on behalf of Anindosta Studios; my apologies for any shortcomings
Wassalamualaikum Warahmatullahi Wabarakatuh